{"sid": "41UBSWLFH527_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 365075, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 365076, "question": "8+3+7+4", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["calc_1", 370758], ["calc_5", 371238], ["calc_+", 371758], ["calc_7", 372519], ["calc_=", 373078], ["submit", 375846]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "290", "answered_time": 375846, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "290", "question_time_start": 375847, "question": "3+6+7", "correct_answer": 16, "events": [["submit", 382815]], "time_left_end": "283", "answered_time": 382815, "user_answer": "16", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "283", "question_time_start": 382815, "question": "3+97", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 386048]], "time_left_end": "280", "answered_time": 386048, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "280", "question_time_start": 386048, "question": "4+3+8+6", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 392689]], "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 392689, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 392690, "question": "4+4+17", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["calc_8", 396102], ["calc_+", 396659], ["calc_1", 397144], ["calc_7", 397878], ["calc_=", 398502], ["submit", 401816]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "264", "answered_time": 401816, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "264", "question_time_start": 401816, "question": "7+3+4", "correct_answer": 14, "events": [["submit", 405384]], "time_left_end": "260", "answered_time": 405384, "user_answer": "14", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "260", "question_time_start": 405384, "question": "7+68", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["calc_6", 407190], ["calc_8", 407662], ["calc_+", 408208], ["calc_7", 408726], ["calc_=", 409340], ["submit", 413278]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "252", "answered_time": 413278, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "252", "question_time_start": 413278, "question": "7+43", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 417574]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 417574, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 417574, "question": "9+3", "correct_answer": 12, "events": [["submit", 420022]], "time_left_end": "246", "answered_time": 420022, "user_answer": "12", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "246", "question_time_start": 420022, "question": "7+9", "correct_answer": 16, "events": [["submit", 424998]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 424998, "user_answer": "16", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 424998, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 424998, "question": "6+4", "correct_answer": 10, "events": [["submit", 427445]], "time_left_end": "238", "answered_time": 427445, "user_answer": "10", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "238", "question_time_start": 427446, "question": "4+67", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["submit", 430862]], "time_left_end": "235", "answered_time": 430862, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "235", "question_time_start": 430862, "question": "3+6+8", "correct_answer": 17, "events": [["submit", 435849]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 435849, "user_answer": "17", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 435850, "question": "7+8+7+6", "correct_answer": 28, "events": [["submit", 442694]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 442694, "user_answer": "28", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 442694, "question": "3+88", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 447042]], "time_left_end": "219", "answered_time": 447042, "user_answer": "81", "user_correct": "False", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "219", "question_time_start": 447043, "question": "8+13", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 454990]], "time_left_end": "211", "answered_time": 454990, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "211", "question_time_start": 454990, "question": "8+4+9", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 459966]], "time_left_end": "206", "answered_time": 459966, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "206", "question_time_start": 459966, "question": "3+7+7+3", "correct_answer": 20, "events": [["submit", 465766]], "time_left_end": "200", "answered_time": 465766, "user_answer": "20", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "200", "question_time_start": 465766, "question": "6+4+47", "correct_answer": 57, "events": [["submit", 469742]], "time_left_end": "196", "answered_time": 469742, "user_answer": "57", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "196", "question_time_start": 469742, "question": "8+3", "correct_answer": 11, "events": [["submit", 472510]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 472510, "user_answer": "11", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 472510, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 472510, "question": "9+58", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 479665]], "time_left_end": "186", "answered_time": 479665, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "186", "question_time_start": 479665, "question": "6+6", "correct_answer": 12, "events": [["submit", 481438]], "time_left_end": "184", "answered_time": 481438, "user_answer": "12", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "184", "question_time_start": 481438, "question": "9+58", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 487934]], "time_left_end": "178", "answered_time": 487934, "user_answer": "57", "user_correct": "False", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "178", "question_time_start": 487934, "question": "8+3+8", "correct_answer": 19, "events": [["submit", 494902]], "time_left_end": "171", "answered_time": 494902, "user_answer": "20", "user_correct": "False", "score": "18"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "171", "question_time_start": 494903, "question": "7+7+4", "correct_answer": 18, "events": [["submit", 498734]], "time_left_end": "167", "answered_time": 498734, "user_answer": "18", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "167", "question_time_start": 498734, "question": "3+4+64", "correct_answer": 71, "events": [["calc_7", 501454], ["calc_+", 501864], ["calc_6", 502502], ["calc_4", 503766], ["calc_=", 504405], ["submit", 507536]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "158", "answered_time": 507536, "user_answer": "71", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "158", "question_time_start": 507536, "question": "7+7+6+4", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 514765]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 514765, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 514766, "question": "7+73", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 518031]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 518031, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 518031, "question": "6+3+7+9", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 525838]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 525838, "user_answer": "28", "user_correct": "False", "score": "21"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 525838, "question": "3+8", "correct_answer": 11, "events": [["submit", 530145]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 530145, "user_answer": "11", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 530145, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 530145, "question": "7+7+37", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["calc_3", 535070], ["calc_7", 536037], ["calc_+", 536686], ["calc_1", 537158], ["calc_4", 537526], ["calc_=", 538070], ["submit", 542622]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "123", "answered_time": 542622, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "123", "question_time_start": 542622, "question": "4+8+3", "correct_answer": 15, "events": [["submit", 549378]], "time_left_end": "116", "answered_time": 549378, "user_answer": "15", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "116", "question_time_start": 549378, "question": "9+8+9", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 556718]], "time_left_end": "109", "answered_time": 556718, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "109", "question_time_start": 556718, "question": "7+53", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 560110]], "time_left_end": "105", "answered_time": 560110, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "105", "question_time_start": 560110, "question": "3+6+6+7", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 565030]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 565030, "user_answer": "32", "user_correct": "False", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 565030, "question": "6+6+6+4", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 571878]], "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 571878, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 571878, "question": "6+84", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 574970]], "time_left_end": "91", "answered_time": 574970, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "91", "question_time_start": 574971, "question": "8+7", "correct_answer": 15, "events": [["submit", 578258]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 578258, "user_answer": "15", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 578258, "question": "8+17", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 581270]], "time_left_end": "84", "answered_time": 581270, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "84", "question_time_start": 581270, "question": "6+3", "correct_answer": 9, "events": [["submit", 583830]], "time_left_end": "82", "answered_time": 583830, "user_answer": "9", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 583830, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "82", "question_time_start": 583830, "question": "6+8+3+7", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 593125]], "time_left_end": "72", "answered_time": 593125, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "72", "question_time_start": 593125, "question": "8+9+7", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 601190]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 601190, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 601190, "question": "9+99", "correct_answer": 108, "events": [["submit", 606838]], "time_left_end": "59", "answered_time": 606838, "user_answer": "108", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "59", "question_time_start": 606839, "question": "9+4+4+4", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 614979]], "time_left_end": "51", "answered_time": 614979, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "51", "question_time_start": 614979, "question": "8+3+8", "correct_answer": 19, "events": [["submit", 618317]], "time_left_end": "47", "answered_time": 618317, "user_answer": "19", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "47", "question_time_start": 618318, "question": "4+13", "correct_answer": 17, "events": [["submit", 620799]], "time_left_end": "45", "answered_time": 620799, "user_answer": "17", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "45", "question_time_start": 620799, "question": "6+4", "correct_answer": 10, "events": [["submit", 624470]], "time_left_end": "41", "answered_time": 624470, "user_answer": "10", "user_correct": "True", "score": "37"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "41", "question_time_start": 624470, "question": "6+49", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 629181]], "time_left_end": "36", "answered_time": 629181, "user_answer": "55", "user_correct": "True", "score": "38"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "36", "question_time_start": 629181, "question": "9+8+29", "correct_answer": 46, "events": [["submit", 636518]], "time_left_end": "29", "answered_time": 636518, "user_answer": "46", "user_correct": "True", "score": "39"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "29", "question_time_start": 636518, "question": "6+9", "correct_answer": 15, "events": [["submit", 641709]], "time_left_end": "24", "answered_time": 641709, "user_answer": "15", "user_correct": "True", "score": "40"}}}, "block_5": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 641709, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "24", "question_time_start": 641709, "question": "7+7+6+7", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 645942]], "time_left_end": "20", "answered_time": 645942, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "41"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "20", "question_time_start": 645942, "question": "4+79", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 652332]], "time_left_end": "13", "answered_time": 652332, "user_answer": "83", "user_correct": "True", "score": "42"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "13", "question_time_start": 652332, "question": "4+7", "correct_answer": 11, "events": [["submit", 655309]], "time_left_end": "10", "answered_time": 655309, "user_answer": "11", "user_correct": "True", "score": "43"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "10", "question_time_start": 655310, "question": "3+59", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 662981]], "time_left_end": "3", "answered_time": 662981, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "44"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "3", "question_time_start": 662982, "question": "9+4+6", "correct_answer": 19, "events": []}}}}}